♫Manage the landing♪
♫ I am super Ready , I quickly have ♪
♫ The Weapon that everyone wants ♫
♫ I kill you quietly, you're shabby ♫
♫ I see your trap stuck to the ceiling ♫
♫ Dude, you're going to do in your pants ♫
I see you in the distance, you remain static
I'm going to shoot you in the head, so I'm going to ...
I manage my 1vs1 easily
Back to reality
I'm not Gotaga, I'm squeezie
and this guy on a distant roof
who snipe and has a big killfeed
and this player who camps in the toilet
Who drinks his shield potion
And this unpleasant feeling
to be late in the storm
and those black thoughts that are going through you
when you lose to the opposing player
I watch Stream to train
But I remain a nil player
at each game my name is Bambi
Easy to kill, like squeezie
*Refrain :I wanted to make top 1
*without the help of any buddy*
*without the power of a fairground*
*Neither the charisma of a villain*
I wanted to make top 1
without the help of any buddy
without the power of a fairground
Neither the charisma of a villain
I did shit, I'm scornful
He killed me even though he is ten years old
I still miss component
I build so slowly that it's exhausting
I made stairs, I put my springboard
I enjoyed it . he broke the base
Days to try the top 1 without prone
I do a beautiful thing. on the network I share it
I'm dragging on the map
to every enemy I panic
I sweat to ball
I will be better on the titanic
I drink a big potion before the little potion
I put a campfire, while I have a medikit
I am aiming at the lamppost instead of the guy
I break all the walls to find the chest
Every time I get one shot at the shotgun
if there is a beautiful skin in the shop.
I missed an offer
I watch Stream to train
But I remain a nil player
at each game my name is Bambi
Easy to kill, like squeezie
*REFRAIN*
I want to make top 1 me
Traduction by *in the description ↓↓↓*